Hilpert, Elmer E. Arbitration Papers 5493
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaPorte, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1319, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  6/23/57. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaPorte, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1319, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  6/27/57. Issue: recall
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaPorte, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1319, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  6/26/57. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaPorte, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1319, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  6/24/57. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaPorte, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1319, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  6/25/57. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaPorte, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1319, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  2/7/57. Issue: rates of pay - new jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaPorte, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1319, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  3/26/58. Issue: classification of jobs - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaPorte, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1319, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  1/28/61. Issue: rates of pay - shift differentials
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaPorte, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1319, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  2/18/61. Issue: classification of jobs - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaPorte, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1319, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  3/11/61. Issue: reduction in force - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaPorte, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1319, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  2/21/61. Issue: rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaPorte, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1319, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaPorte, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1319, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  10/28/60. Withdrawn
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaPorte, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1319, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  7/19/63. Issue: recall - failure to report
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., LaPorte, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1319, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  8/5/63. Issue: rates of pay - new job
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Norwood, Ohio vs. IUE, Local 765, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  11/4/65. Issue: automation - assignment of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania vs. UAW, Local l036, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  5/17/63. Issue: rates of pay - change in product
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania vs. UAW, Local l036, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  5/19/63. Issue: recall - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local l027, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  6/1/53. Withdrawn
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local l027, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  6/2/53. Issue: vacation pay - computation
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local l027, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  5/16/53. Issue: lay-off - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local l027, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  6/3/53. Issue: assignment of jobs - temporary assignment
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local l027, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  5/17/53. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  8/10/53. Issue: layoff - recall - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  6/19/53. Issue: overtime- distribution
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  8/11/53. Issue: reduction in force - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  4/10/54. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  6/15/54. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority.
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  4/10/54. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  7/17/54. Issue: rates of pay.
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  6/28/54. Issue: reduction in force - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  6/26/54. Issue: overtime -assignment of.
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  9/30/54. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  10/2/54. Issue: overtime
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  10/12/54. Issue: assignment of jobs - transfer
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  10/10/54. Issue: schedules of work
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  8/26/54. Issue: seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  1/25/55. Issue: discipline- layoff.
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  1/25/55. Issue: layoff-recall
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  3/23/55. Issue: overtime - assignment of
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  3/24/55. Issue: seniority - unit work
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  2/2/55. Issue: transfer -seniority
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  1/27/55. No award
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  5/22/56. Issue: transfers.
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  5/10/56. Issue: rates of pay - shift differentials
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  6/10/56. Issue: rates of pay; transfers
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  9/12/56. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  10/14/56. Issue: rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  9/19/56. Issue: promotions - seniority
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  9/17/56. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  11/9/56. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  5/28/57. Issue: transfers
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  5/26/57. Issue: transfers - seniority
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  6/16/57. Issue: recall - inventory
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  6/12/57. Issue: seniority
- Allis-Chalmer Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  6/3/57. Issue: seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  6/14/57. Issue: seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  10/21/57. Issue: assignment of jobs - assignment to work outside unit
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  1/4/58. Issue: overtime - assignment of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  11/25/57. Issue: rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  11/28/57. Issue: employees' rights - union representation
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  11/11/57. Issue: classification of jobs - new job
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  6/7/57. Withdrawn
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  6/7/57. Settled
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Springfield, Illinois vs. UAW, Local 1027, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  4/16/63. Issue: discharge
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  8/7/54. Issue: lunch periods - three shift operation
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  8/5/54. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  8/20/54. Issue: assignment of jobs - overtime
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  8/22/54. Issue: classification of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  9/30/54. Issue: transfers - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  5/14/55. Issue: classification of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  5/22/55. Issue: overtime -assignment of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  5/23/55. Issue: overtime -assignment of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  5/25/55. Issue: overtime
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  5/31/55. Issue: seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  4/7/55. Withdrawn
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  4/7/55. Settled
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  5/12/55. Issue: discharge; reinstatement
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  6/22/55. Issue: overtime -assignment of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  6/23/55. Issue: classification of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  11/10/55. Withdrawn
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  11/10/55. Settled
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  11/10/55. Issue: overtime
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  1/26/56. Issue: overtime -improper assignment - remedy
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  9/25/56. Issue: overtime
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  2/26/56. Issue: overtime
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  10/6/56. Issue: rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  12/27/56. Issue: classification of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  12/31/56. Issue: rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  1/1/57. Issue: rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  1/2/57. Issue: classification of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  9/26/56. Issue: overtime
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  3/15/57. Issue: overtime
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  3/15/57. Issue: layoff as discipline
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  3/20/57. Issue: overtime
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  3/19/57. Issue: overtime
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  3/23/57. Issue: classification of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  5/17/57. Issue: transfer -promotion
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  12/13/56. Withdrawn
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  12/13/56. Settled
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  5/19/57. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  5/23/57. Settled
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  9/2/57. Issue: overtime - call in
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  9/4/57. Issue: transfer - temporary - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  5/23/57. Withdrawn
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  10/11/57. Issue: classification of jobs - change in work assignment
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  10/20/57. Issue: transfer - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  1/3/61. Issue: layoff - vacation pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  1/7/61. Issue: seniority -transfer
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  1/10/61. Issue: overtime -call in
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  1/12/61. Issue: overtime -assignment
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  4/14/61. Issue: vacation pay - layoff
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  5/22/61. Issue: reduction in workforce - transfer
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  5/24/61. Issue: reduction in workforce - transfer
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  3/3/61. Issue: reduction in workforce - transfer
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  3/23/62. Issue: layoff - vacation pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  2/2/62. Issue: reduction in force - transfer
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  4/10/63. Issue: contracting out - bargaining unit work; layoff - insurance eligibility
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  11/7/62. Issue: layoff - insurance eligibility; shutdown - assignment of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., Terre Haute, Indiana vs. UAW, Local 1164, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  11/6/63. Issue: contracting out - bargaining unit work
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 268, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  1/31/54. Issue: discharge
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 268, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  3/26/54. Issue: rates of pay - reduction
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 268, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  3/10/54. Issue: union representation and business - dues
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 268, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  4/17/54. Issue: Assignment of jobs - assignment to work outside unit
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 268, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  4/15/54. Issue: rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  8/30/54. Issue: classification of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  8/9/54. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  8/11/54. Issue: reduction in force - assignment of jobs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  9/19/54. Issue: recall - transfers
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  9/17/54. Issue: discipline
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  3/28/55. Issue: transfers - seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  3/30/55. Issue: seniority - super seniority.
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  12/2/54. Settled
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  2/8/56. Issue: rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  5/1/55. Issue: rates of pay - downtime.
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  4/6/55. Issue: arbitrability - jurisdiction; transfers
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  4/4/55. Issue: layoff
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  6/28/56. Issue: layoff
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  2/6/56. Issue: transfer
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  7/17/56. Issue: transfer -seniority
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  6/14/56. Issue: layoff
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  6/18/56. Issue: discipline
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  10/21/56. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  10/23/56. Issue: rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  11/16/56. Issue: rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  7/17/56. Issue: layoffs
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  11/14/56. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  7/16/56. Issue: layoff
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  1/25/57. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  6/22/56. Issue: rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  6/24/56. Issue: rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  9/3/56. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  1/27/57. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  1/29/57. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  2/13/57. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  2/15/57. Issue: transfers - seniority - reduction in workforce
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  2/17/57. Issue: union representation and business
- Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co., West Allis, Wisconsin vs. UAW, Local 248, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 8)